Finding Aid for the Office of the Chancellor. Administrative files of Charles E. Young. UARC.0594
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Index: BB33/S4D. Systemwide Admin & Acad. Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Sex Discrimination - UCLA Campus., 1972-1974. (Box 204, Folder 7)
- Index: DA52/Spec. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Files - Speeches., 1996. (Box 205, Folder 1)
- Index: DA75. Campus Administration & LA Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Staff Files - Executive Vice Chancellor - (Speeches of Rich & Kennel)., 1992-1997. (Box 205, Folder 10)
- Index: DA52/Spec. Campus Administration & Los Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Files - Speeches., 1997. (Box 205, Folder 2)
- Index: RC34. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Student & Academic Affairs Section., 1962-1987. (Box 205, Folder 3)
- Index: RF52. Student Services & Activities - Placement Services., 1974-1991. (Box 205, Folder 4)
- Index: RF87. Student Services & Activities - Registrar - Schedule of Classes & Catalog., 1971-1994. (Box 205, Folder 5)
- Index: RF87. Student Services & Activities - Registrar - Schedule of Classes & Catalog., 1991-1994. (Box 205, Folder 6)
- Index: RF88. Student Services & Activities - Registrar - Regulations for Undergraduate Students., 1974-1983. (Box 205, Folder 7)
- Index: S37. Student Associations - Associated Students - Board of Communications - Press., 1973. (Box 205, Folder 8)
- Index: S58. Student Associations - Associated Students - Student Welfare Commission., 1978-1986. (Box 205, Folder 9)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1970-1975. (Box 206, Folder 1)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1975-1977. (Box 206, Folder 2)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1974-1977. (Box 206, Folder 3)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1977. (Box 206, Folder 4)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1975-1979. (Box 206, Folder 5)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1977-1979. (Box 206, Folder 6)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General - (cont. 3 Yr Enrollment Plan - Grad & Prof Educ)., 1983-1986. (Box 207)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1972-1988. (Box 207)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1976-1978. (Box 207, Folder 1)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1977-1979. (Box 207, Folder 2)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General (3-Yr enrollment plan graduate & professional education)., 1980-1982. (Box 207, Folder 3)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1980-1983. (Box 207, Folder 4)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General - (3 Yr Enrollment Plan Grad & Prof Students)., 1979-1983. (Box 207, Folder 5)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1983. (Box 207, Folder 6)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1983-1986. (Box 208, Folder 1)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1984-1987. (Box 208, Folder 2)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1988-1994. (Box 208, Folder 3)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1986-1990. (Box 208, Folder 4)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1972-1988. (Box 208, Folder 5)
- Index: RC28. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admissions & Recruitment - General., 1991-1994. (Box 208, Folder 6)
- Index: R88/P8. Student Services & Activities - Cultural & Recreational Affairs - Services & Facilities - Baseball Stadium - Public Relations., 1971-1974. (Box 209, Folder 1)
- Index: R88/P8. Student Services & Activities - Cultural & Recreational Affairs - Services & Facilities - Baseball Stadium - Public Relations., 1975-1976. (Box 209, Folder 2)
- Index: RF61. Student Services & Activities - Placement Services - Placement & Career Planning Center., 1971-1983. (Box 209, Folder 3)
- Index: RF61. Student Services & Activities - Placement Services - Placement & Career Planning Center., 1972-1981. (Box 209, Folder 4)
- Index: RF61. Student Services & Activities - Placement Services - Placement & Career Planning Center., 1982-1993. (Box 209, Folder 5)
- Index: RF55. Student Services & Activities - Placement Services - Educational Career Services., 1973-1977. (Box 209, Folder 6)
- Index: RF78. Student Services & Activities - Registrar - General., 1971-1977. (Box 209, Folder 7)
- Index: RI13 & RI16. Student Services & Activities - Special Progs for Minority & Disadvantaged Students - Reg & Orientation; URD - Students., 1971-1975. (Box 210, Folder 1)
- Index: RA59. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - University & Campus Loan Sources (Intramural)., 1978-1983. (Box 210, Folder 10)
- Index: RC31-Rpts. Student Services & Activities - Graduate Division - Admission & Recruitment - Minority Admission - Reports., 1970-1973. (Box 210, Folder 2)
- Index: RH1. Student Services & Activities - Religious Facilities & Activities - General., 1973-1983. (Box 210, Folder 3)
- Index: RH3. Student Services & Activities - Religious Facilities & Activities - University Religious Conference - General., 1979-1990. (Box 210, Folder 4)
- Index: RH4. Student Services & Activities - Religious Facilities & Activities - University Religious Conference - Administration & Staff., 1979-1993. (Box 210, Folder 5)
- Index: RF90. Student Services & Activities - Registrar - Transcripts and Student Records., 1969-1978. (Box 210, Folder 6)
- Index: RF90. Student Services & Activities - Registrar - Transcripts and Student Records., 1981-1994. (Box 210, Folder 7)
- Index: RF90/C6. Student Services & Activities - Registrar - Transcripts and Student Records - Confidentiality of Student Records., 1968-1992. (Box 210, Folder 8)
- Index: RA71. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Extramural - California., 1970-1975. (Box 210, Folder 9)
- Index: RA1. Student Services & Activities -- Financial Aid - Administration & Staff., 1973-1988. (Box 211, Folder 1)
- Index: RA4. Student Services & Activities -- Financial Aid - Administration & Staff., 1970-1976. (Box 211, Folder 2)
- Index: RA4. Student Services & Activities -- Financial Aid - Administration & Staff., 1974-1987. (Box 211, Folder 3)
- Index: RA4. Student Services & Activities -- Financial Aid - Administration & Staff., 1981-1989. (Box 211, Folder 4)
- Index: RA4. Student Services & Activities -- Financial Aid - Administration & Staff., 1984-1994. (Box 211, Folder 5)
- Index: RA4/F4. Student Services & Activities -- Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - Student Federal Financial Aid Programs., 1973-1979. (Box 211, Folder 6)
- Index: RA4/F4. Student Services & Activities -- Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - Student Federal Financial Aid Programs., 1982-1996. (Box 211, Folder 7)
- Index: RA89-Pres. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Work Study Programs - President., 1970-1973. (Box 212, Folder 1)
- Index: RA89-Fed. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Work Study - Federal., 1971-1986. (Box 212, Folder 2)
- Index: RA89. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Work Study., 1970-1990. (Box 212, Folder 3)
- Index: DA16/C4. Campus Administration & Loa Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Admin & Adv Cmtes - Child Care Advisory Committee., 1974-1977. (Box 212, Folder 4)
- Index: DA16/C3. Campus Administration & Loa Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Admin & Adv Cmtes - Campus Computing Committee., 1971-1981. (Box 212, Folder 5)
- Index: DA16/C3. Campus Administration & Loa Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Admin & Adv Cmtes - Campus Computing Committee., 1977-1984. (Box 212, Folder 6)
- Index: DA16/C3. Campus Administration & Loa Angeles Division Academic Senate - Chancellor's Office - Chancellor's Admin & Adv Cmtes - Campus Computing Committee., 1985-1989. (Box 212, Folder 7)
- Index: BB33/C. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UC Employees., 1973-1995. (Box 213, Folder 1)
- Index: BB33/D. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus., 1970-1988. (Box 213, Folder 2)
- Index: BB33/D1. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Preparation of the Plan., 1970-1973. (Box 213, Folder 3)
- Index: BB33/D1-Plan. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Preparation of the Plan - Plan., 1973. (Box 213, Folder 4)
- Index: BB33/D1-Plan. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Preparation of the Plan - Plan., 1973. (Box 213, Folder 5)
- Index: BB33/D1-Plan. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - UCLA Campus - Preparation of the Plan - Plan., 1973-1974. (Box 213, Folder 6)
- Index: BB33/S4J. Systemwide Administration & Academic Senate - Administration - Affirmative Action - Discrimination on the Basis of Sex - Coopn with Gvnmtl Agencies., 1980-1983. (Box 213, Folder 7)
- Index: RA10/H4E4. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Extramural - US DHEW - Office of Education., 1977-1995. (Box 213, Folder 8)
- Index: RA10/H4. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Extramural - U.S. - Dept of Health, Education and Welfare., 1983-1994. (Box 213, Folder 9)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1965-1977. (Box 214, Folder 1)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1972-1981. (Box 214, Folder 2)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1982-1983. (Box 214, Folder 3)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1985-1988. (Box 214, Folder 4)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1977-1989. (Box 214, Folder 5)
- Index: RA53-03. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources - Direct Government Lending., 1991-1992. (Box 214, Folder 6)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1992-1993. (Box 214, Folder 7)
- Index: RA53-03. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources - Direct Student Lending., 1993. (Box 214, Folder 8)
- Index: RA53-03. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources - Direct Government Lending., 1993-1994. (Box 215, Folder 1)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1987-1994. (Box 215, Folder 2)
- Index: RA53-03. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources - Direct Government Lending., 1994-1995. (Box 215, Folder 3)
- Index: RA53. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Loans - Government Loan Sources., 1992-1997. (Box 215, Folder 4)
- Index: RA74-D. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Extramural - Private Sources., 1970-1996. (Box 215, Folder 5)
- Index: RA74-E. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Extramural - Private Sources., 1980-1996. (Box 215, Folder 6)
- Index: RA74-M-N. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Extramural - Private Sources., 1976-1996. (Box 215, Folder 7)
- Index: RA74- (O-P). Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Extramural - Private Sources., 1972-1994. (Box 216, Folder 1)
- Index: RA74-(R-S). Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Extramural - Private Sources., 1969-1996. (Box 216, Folder 2)
- Index: RA74-T. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Extramural - Private Sources., 1989-1996. (Box 216, Folder 3)
- Index: RA77. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Intramural., 1971-1982. (Box 216, Folder 4)
- Index: RA77. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Intramural., 1975-1985. (Box 216, Folder 5)
- Index: RA77. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Scholarships - Intramural., 1981-1995. (Box 216, Folder 6)
- Index: IB10/R4. Public Relations - Cooperation, Aid & Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Research Universities Network (RUN)., 1980-1992. (Box 216, Folder 7)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1961-1981. (Box 217, Folder 1)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1979-1980. (Box 217, Folder 2)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1981-1982. (Box 217, Folder 3)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1983-1984. (Box 217, Folder 4)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1981-1985. (Box 217, Folder 5)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1981-1987. (Box 217, Folder 6)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1981-1987. (Box 218, Folder 1)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1983-1988. (Box 218, Folder 2)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1983-1988. (Box 218, Folder 3)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1988-1992. (Box 218, Folder 4)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1988-1994. (Box 218, Folder 5)
- Index: RA4/S7. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Administration & Staff - UC Student Financial Aid Funds., 1971-1994. (Box 218, Folder 6)
- Index: IB10/O7. Public Relations - Cooperation, Aid & Information for outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Organization for Tropical Studies., 1971-1988. (Box 218, Folder 7)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 January-February. (Box 219, Folder 1)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 February. (Box 219, Folder 2)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 May. (Box 219, Folder 3)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 May. (Box 219, Folder 4)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 August. (Box 219, Folder 5)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1995. (Box 219, Folder 6)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 June. (Box 220, Folder 1)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 July. (Box 220, Folder 2)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 August-September. (Box 220, Folder 3)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 September-October. (Box 220, Folder 4)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1991 January-February. (Box 221, Folder 1)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1990 October-1991 July. (Box 221, Folder 2)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1991 August. (Box 221, Folder 3)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1991 September-October. (Box 221, Folder 4)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1991 December-1992 April. (Box 221, Folder 5)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1991 March-1992 February. (Box 222, Folder 1)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1992 July-October. (Box 222, Folder 2)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1992 October-December. (Box 222, Folder 3)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1993 March-June. (Box 222, Folder 4)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1993-1995. (Box 222, Folder 5)
- Index: IB10/K5. PR - Cooperation, Aid, Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof Orgs & Societies - Knight Foundation Commission on Intercollegiate Athletics., 1994. (Box 222, Folder 5)
- Index: K49 ( -A). Extramural Support - Private Sources (-A)., 1973-1986. (Box 223, Folder 1)
- Index: K49-(C-G). Extramural Support - Private Sources (C-G)., 1970-1989. (Box 223, Folder 2)
- Index: K49-(H-I). Extramural Support - Private Sources (H-I)., 1975-1992. (Box 223, Folder 3)
- Index: K49-K. Extramural Support - Private Sources (K)., 1983-1989. (Box 223, Folder 4)
- Index: K49-(L-R). Extramural Support - Private Sources (L-R)., 1973-1989. (Box 223, Folder 5)
- Index: IB10/O7. Public Relations - Cooperation, Aid & Information for Outside Entities - Educ'l & Prof. Org. & Societies - Organization for Tropical Studies., 1968-1994. (Box 223, Folder 6)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1972-1985. (Box 224, Folder 1)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1984-1986. (Box 224, Folder 2)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1984-1987. (Box 224, Folder 3)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1987-1988. (Box 224, Folder 4)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1988-1990. (Box 224, Folder 5)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1989-1993. (Box 224, Folder 6)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1991-1993. (Box 224, Folder 7)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural - (Predoctoral Humanities Fellowship)., 1987-1994. (Box 225, Folder 1)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1993-1995. (Box 225, Folder 2)
- Index: RA28. Student Services & Activities - Financial Aid - Fellowships - Intramural., 1989-1996. (Box 225, Folder 3)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1987-1992. (Box 225, Folder 4)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils - (Mand Ret Proj)., 1989. (Box 225, Folder 5)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1991-1993. (Box 225, Folder 6)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1988-1994. (Box 226, Folder 1)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1993. (Box 226, Folder 2)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1988-1996. (Box 226, Folder 3)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1996. (Box 226, Folder 4)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1987-1997. (Box 226, Folder 5)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & LA Div Academic Senate - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Membership on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1996-1997. (Box 226, Folder 6)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & Los Angeles Div Acad Sen. - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Mbrship on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1970-1974. (Box 227, Folder 1)
- Index: DA69. Campus Admin & Los Angeles Div Acad Sen. - Chancellor's Ofc - Chancellor's Files - Mbrship on Outside Committees, Boards & Councils., 1973. (Box 227, Folder 2)